Ada Mandala

Consultant Software Engineer

Contact

Professional Summary

785-424-0182 📞 ada.mandala@pm.me Lawrence, KS 66049 cubething.dev #

Passionate software developer with a strong interest in systems-level programming and 4 years of experience. I hope to continue working with low-level languages. Frequently praised as diligent and insightful by peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals. I hope to use my interest in theoretical foundations and my practical insight to fulfill the Software Engineer role at your company.

Relevant Skills

Rust

C(++)

HTTP(S)/TLS

Linux SysAdmin

Python

WASM

Git CLI

Experience

Software Engineer

Valorem Reply | Jun 2022 - Present

- Worked with Disney to bring ESPN+ to the PS5.
- Designed and implemented business critical systems for commerce and analytics.
- Developed automation and process improvement, hosting the team scripts repository
- Lead department training exercise within 5 months of employment.

Front-End Web Developer

Roll20 | Oct 2019 - Aug 2021

- Brought static design documents to life for the Roll20 Virtual Desktop.
- Integrated interactive user experiences for the original game Burn Bryte.
- Designed and developed local dev environment tool Mimic.

Client Delivery and Maintanence Specialist

PriceSpider | Mar 2019 - Oct 2019

• Starting as a maintanence specialist, I negotiated with management to build and lead the first team of frontend engineers at the Kansas City location.

Freelance Developer

Freelance | Jun 2018 - Jun 2022

- Designed, developed, and integrated full-stack solutions to meet client needs
- Worked with clients on various platforms and in various industries including web, mobile, and desktop applications.

Projects



Personal | Apr 2019 - Apr 2022

 Designed and developed a game engine capable of real-time editing, rendering 3D graphics, and running on web and desktop with WASM and WGPU.

Education

Mathematics and Philosophy, BA, Honors

University of Kansas | 2017

Relevant Courses

Awards and Honors

Theory of Computation Graph Theory

Paretsky Award for Creativity Morse Scholarship for Excellence in Philosophy